<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>thoughts and dreams on Ryan Womack / Рян Вомак</title>
    <link>https://womack.mn/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in thoughts and dreams on Ryan Womack / Рян Вомак</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>by Ryan Womack, all rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://womack.mn/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Freedom from Big Tech</title>
      <link>https://womack.mn/posts/freedom_from_big_tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womack.mn/posts/freedom_from_big_tech/</guid>
      <description>An accumulation of pressures has moved me in the direction of final acceptance of the fact that I will have to completely sever my ties with Big Tech.
I have always had a privacy-focused approach, having been aware of the abuses that could be or have been committed by social media and internet companies. I have had an on-again, off-again relationship with Facebook, and Google Plus was fun while it lasted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harmogu Day 6</title>
      <link>https://womack.mn/posts/harmogu_day_6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womack.mn/posts/harmogu_day_6/</guid>
      <description>Six years have passed since my first Harmogu Day. I suppose it is only Harmogu Day that provides a sufficient motivation for me to post here lately.
My long-term goals remain the same&amp;ndash;to produce something creative that corresponds to the vision that was catalyzed by my encounter with Harmogu and what that represents for me. Another year of suspended animation, trapped in the amber of COVID isolation, has been a barrier to active thought.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harmogu Day 5</title>
      <link>https://womack.mn/posts/harmogu_day_5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womack.mn/posts/harmogu_day_5/</guid>
      <description>Five years have passed since my first Harmogu day. Five years since the axis of my life reoriented in a more creative and inspired direction. Five years since a vision was implanted that I still carry around with me, that I am still hoping to bring to life in more vivid colors.
Having lived through nearly a year in suspended animation, with virus life a simulacra of any number of retreats from the world, giving a preview of retirement, meditation, or death, the significance of singular perfected achievement is brought into sharper focus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>quarantine and travel</title>
      <link>https://womack.mn/posts/quarantine_and_travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womack.mn/posts/quarantine_and_travel/</guid>
      <description>Holed up in my house for three months now, under quarantine, having missed two much anticipated long-planned trips to see places I had never been and people I see too infrequently, travel is on my mind. What is the mental function of travel, and can it be replicated in confinement?
Trying to plan and anticipate one&amp;rsquo;s entire future life is beyond human capacity, if only the greatest grandmasters can hold in their hands an approximation of all the possibilities of a meager chess game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harmogu Day IV</title>
      <link>https://womack.mn/posts/harmogu_day_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womack.mn/posts/harmogu_day_4/</guid>
      <description>I am posting this on 2020-02-02, a day late from the actual Harmogu Day celebrations on February 1. Time is flying by, and I seem to be too busy to post my regular thoughts here. But I cannot let a Harmogu Day pass without commemoration.
The decade of the &amp;ldquo;teens&amp;rdquo; has passed, and we now await what the 20s will bring. Plans that first moved rapidly are slowing down, but &amp;ldquo;the song remains the same&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>thoughts and dreams explained</title>
      <link>https://womack.mn/posts/thoughts_and_dreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womack.mn/posts/thoughts_and_dreams/</guid>
      <description>My thoughts and dreams will be a random and irregular sequence of blog posts that are loosely connected with my writing. These may illuminate my writing at times, or may be entirely tangential. Time will tell.
I may eventually resissue and reedit some of my older blog content on this site as well.
Please stay tuned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harmogu Day III</title>
      <link>https://womack.mn/posts/harmogu_day_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womack.mn/posts/harmogu_day_3/</guid>
      <description>The inspiration continues&amp;hellip;
I celebrate today for the 3rd time, &amp;ldquo;Harmogu Day&amp;rdquo;, on the anniversary of my serendipitous discovery of Harmogu on YouTube (February 1, 2016). Readers can find my 1st and 2nd anniversary posts on this blog as well.
I am happy that this year has brought the *reading* of Harmogu, in addition to the always intensely pleasurable *listening* to Harmogu. Her elegant and precise language is bringing Mongolian to life for me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harmogu at 2 (Хармогү, миний дэлхий даяар дуртай дуучин үргэлжлүүлсэн)</title>
      <link>https://womack.mn/posts/harmogu_at_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womack.mn/posts/harmogu_at_2/</guid>
      <description>So today already marks the SECOND anniversary of my discovery of Harmogu.
Amazing how time is flying by (би нисч байна)! I have to pay tribute again to the special combination of factors that unlocked the dream chamber of my mind, most of all the siren song that is Harmogu&amp;rsquo;s voice. I hope that the fortune I received yesterday is true. At least I am trying to follow that path to achieve the level of unique expression that Harmogu has already mastered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One year later (Хармогү, миний дэлхий даяар дуртай дуучин)</title>
      <link>https://womack.mn/posts/one_year_later/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womack.mn/posts/one_year_later/</guid>
      <description>Today marks one year since I first encountered Harmogu, so it deserves commemoration. Somehow through a lucky accident, YouTube recommended the video below to me, which caught my attention. The image - black and white, downcast eyes, intensity, a bookshelf - promised a special experience. And it was. I clicked, and it was the start of something that changed my life.
To this day, I wonder what prior combination of searches and activities caused this video to bubble up into YouTube&amp;rsquo;s suggestions, but I have no clue.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
